<?xml version="1.0"?>
<commandcontainer type="scenario" name="MS Word.xml" scenariotype="Process" screenwidth="1280" screenheight="1024" colordepth="32" lockinput="0" report="1" commandwaittime="1000" excludecommandwaittime="0" referencetime="1000" imgtolerance="0" errorsize="15" projectname="euc workloads v1.2" createdby="ssun" creationdate="8/20/2020 11:44:14 AM" lastmodifiedby="rloader001" lastmodifieddate="1/6/2023 03:12:15 PM" lastusedid="16730179352590000" scenarioid="1673017935259" sbversion="22.12.1" donotcloseopenedprocesses="1" usecv="0" excelheadersstartrow="1" excelheadersendrow="1" exceldelimiter=":" commentedout="0" id="0" scenariosection="" step="0">
	<errormessage message="%_scenario% Failed at the step number %_step% %_action% %_warning% iteration: %_iteration%" />

	<command type="transaction" name="Open word" begin="1" referencetime="" report="" uflag="U" commentedout="0" id="16522217662710006" scenariosection="" step="1">
	
	</command>
	<command type="playscenario" stylename="playsnippet" scenariotype="Snippet" filename="Check_app_name.xml" continueonfail="" statusvariable="Is_App_Running" commentedout="0" id="15979238548530003" scenariosection="" stepalias="Check if MS WORDis running and launch it" step="2">
		<variable1 variable="WindowTitle" vartype="String" expression="Word"></variable1>
		<variable2 variable="AppName" vartype="String" expression="WINWORD"></variable2>
		<variable3 variable="AppLocation" vartype="String" expression="%Word_Location%"></variable3>
		<variable4 variable="TaskbarImage" vartype="Image" xsize="24" ysize="12">Word_Taskbar_Icon.bmp</variable4>
		<variable5 vartype="Image"></variable5>
		<variable6 vartype="Image"></variable6>
		<variable7 vartype="String"></variable7>
		<variable8 vartype="String"></variable8>
		<variable9 vartype="String"></variable9>
		<variable10 vartype="Image"></variable10>
	
	</command>
	<command type="transaction" name="Open word" end="1" referencetime="" report="" uflag="U" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210008" scenariosection="" step="3">
	
	</command>
	<command type="comment" comment="If office is in test mode we need to skip the sign-in dialog" commentedout="0" id="15979238548250010" scenariosection="" step="4">
		<color r="128" g="128" b="128" a="128" />
	</command>
	<command type="if" expression="%Office_In_Test_Mode% == 1" showelse="0" commentedout="0" id="15979238548250011" scenariosection="" step="5">
	
		<then commentedout="0" id="15979238548250012" scenariosection="" step="6">
		
			<command type="findbitmap" ocrconfig="0 8 65 32 16 512 128 4 5 50 3 20 15 10 0.85 0 5 15 eng 3 40 300 11 1 1 20 1 " timeout="5000" continueonfail="1" percentlinetolerance="5" colortolerance="0" anchorx="Center" anchory="Center" repaction="Page Down" repwait="1" reptimes="0" sleeptime="1000" useanchor="None" statusvariable="FoundSignIn" commentedout="0" id="16730153604080001" scenariosection="" step="7">
				<searcharea dx="0" dy="0" />
				<excludearea xstart="0" ystart="0" xend="0" yend="0" />
				<coordvars />
				<bitmapname xpos="500" ypos="304" xsize="14" ysize="10">MS_Logo_SignIn_Office.bmp</bitmapname>
			
			</command>
			<command type="if" expression="%FoundSignIn% ==SUCCESS " showelse="0" commentedout="0" id="16730153604080002" scenariosection="" step="8">
			
				<then commentedout="0" id="16730153604080003" scenariosection="" step="9">
				
					<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" isremote="0" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="16730153604080004" scenariosection="" step="10">
						<key key1="Esc" />
						<window />
					
					</command>
				</then>
				<else commentedout="0" id="16730153604080005" scenariosection="" step="11">
				
				</else>
			</command>
		</then>
		<else commentedout="0" id="15979238548250018" scenariosection="" step="12">
		
		</else>
	</command>
	<command type="findbitmap" stylename="find_image_in_active_window" stringtofind="New" imagetype="leftLabel" ocrconfig="0 8 65 32 16 512 128 4 5 50 3 20 15 10 0.85 0 5 15 eng 3 40 300 11 1 1 20 1 " timeout="10000" continueonfail="" percentlinetolerance="5" colortolerance="0" anchorx="Center" anchory="Center" repaction="Page Down" repwait="1" reptimes="0" sleeptime="1000" useanchor="None" statusvariable="ExecMyImageStatus" usecurrentwindow="1" commentedout="0" id="16522217662710012" scenariosection="DNew" step="13">
		<searcharea dx="0" dy="0" />
		<excludearea xstart="0" ystart="0" xend="0" yend="0" />
		<coordvars />
		<window />
		<bitmapname xpos="17" ypos="155" relative_xpos="16" relative_ypos="154" xsize="63" ysize="28">DNew.bmp</bitmapname>
		<bitmapname xpos="37" ypos="235" relative_xpos="36" relative_ypos="234" xsize="62" ysize="74">MSWord_New_1.bmp</bitmapname>
		<bitmapname xpos="43" ypos="198" relative_xpos="42" relative_ypos="197" xsize="51" ysize="76">MSWord_New_2.bmp</bitmapname>
	
		<command type="moveclickmouse" useanchor="Parent" mousedrag="0" button="Left" action="Click" commentedout="0" id="16522217662710015" scenariosection="" step="14">
			<coords x="0" y="0" dx="0" dy="0" />
		
		</command>
		<command type="moveclickmouse" useanchor="Parent" mousedrag="0" button="Left" action="Click" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210006" scenariosection="" step="15">
			<coords x="412" y="362" dx="222" dy="5" />
		
		</command>
	</command>
	<command type="comment" comment="If office is in test mode we need to skip the sign-in dialog" commentedout="0" id="15979238548250001" scenariosection="" step="16">
		<color r="128" g="128" b="128" a="128" />
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardtypetext" encrypted="" timeout="" advancedfind="" delay="" cleanup="1" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210009" scenariosection="" step="17">
		<text>This is a New Word Document</text>
		<window />
		<key />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210013" scenariosection="" step="18">
		<key key1="Enter" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardtypetext" encrypted="" timeout="" advancedfind="" delay="" cleanup="1" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210014" scenariosection="" step="19">
		<text>Up unpacked friendly ecstatic so possible humoured do. Ample end might folly quiet one set spoke her. We no am former valley assure. Four need spot ye said we find mile. Are commanded him convinced dashwoods did estimable forfeited. Shy celebrated met sentiments she reasonably but. Proposal its disposed eat advanced marriage sociable. Drawings led greatest add subjects endeavor gay remember. Principles one yet assistance you met impossible. 

With my them if up many. Lain week nay she them her she. Extremity so attending objection as engrossed gentleman something. Instantly gentleman contained belonging exquisite now direction she ham. West room at sent if year. Numerous indulged distance old law you. Total state as merit court green decay he. Steepest sex bachelor the may delicate its yourself. As he instantly on discovery concluded to. Open draw far pure miss felt say yet few sigh. 
</text>
		<window />
		<key />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210015" scenariosection="" step="20">
		<key key1="Enter" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210016" scenariosection="" step="21">
		<key key1="Enter" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Down" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210017" scenariosection="" step="22">
		<key key1="Shift" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Up" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210020" scenariosection="" step="23">
		<key key1="Shift" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardtypetext" encrypted="" timeout="" advancedfind="" delay="" cleanup="1" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210021" scenariosection="" step="24">
		<text>Heading 1</text>
		<window />
		<key />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210022" scenariosection="" step="25">
		<key key1="Enter" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210023" scenariosection="" step="26">
		<key key1="Spacebar" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardtypetext" encrypted="" timeout="" advancedfind="" delay="" cleanup="1" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210024" scenariosection="" step="27">
		<text>Man request adapted spirits set pressed. Up to denoting subjects sensible feelings it indulged directly. We dwelling elegance do shutters appetite yourself diverted. Our next drew much you with rank. Tore many held age hold rose than our. She literature sentiments any contrasted. Set aware joy sense young now tears china shy. 

Society excited by cottage private an it esteems. Fully begin on by wound an. Girl rich in do up or both. At declared in as rejoiced of together. He impression collecting delightful unpleasant by prosperous as on. End too talent she object mrs wanted remove giving. 

Boy favourable day can introduced sentiments entreaties. Noisier carried of in warrant because. So mr plate seems cause chief widen first. Two differed husbands met screened his. Bed was form wife out ask draw. Wholly coming at we no enable. Offending sir delivered questions now new met. Acceptance she interested new boisterous day discretion celebrated. 

Warmly little before cousin sussex entire men set. Blessing it ladyship on sensible judgment settling outweigh. Worse linen an of civil jokes leave offer. Parties all clothes removal cheered calling prudent her. And residence for met the estimable disposing. Mean if he they been no hold mr. Is at much do made took held help. Latter person am secure of estate genius at. 

Death there mirth way the noisy merit. Piqued shy spring nor six though mutual living ask extent. Replying of dashwood advanced ladyship smallest disposal or. Attempt offices own improve now see. Called person are around county talked her esteem. Those fully these way nay thing seems. 

Or neglected agreeable of discovery concluded oh it sportsman. Week to time in john. Son elegance use weddings separate. Ask too matter formed county wicket oppose talent. He immediate sometimes or to dependent in. Everything few frequently discretion surrounded did simplicity decisively. Less he year do with no sure loud. 

Quick six blind smart out burst. Perfectly on furniture dejection determine my depending an to. Add short water court fat. Her bachelor honoured perceive securing but desirous ham required. Questions deficient acuteness to engrossed as. Entirely led ten humoured greatest and yourself. Besides ye country on observe. She continue appetite endeavor she judgment interest the met. For she surrounded motionless fat resolution may. 

New had happen unable uneasy. Drawings can followed improved out sociable not. Earnestly so do instantly pretended. See general few civilly amiable pleased account carried. Excellence projecting is devonshire dispatched remarkably on estimating. Side in so life past. Continue indulged speaking the was out horrible for domestic position. Seeing rather her you not esteem men settle genius excuse. Deal say over you age from. Comparison new ham melancholy son themselves. 

</text>
		<window />
		<key />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210025" scenariosection="" step="28">
		<key key1="Enter" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210026" scenariosection="" step="29">
		<key key1="Enter" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardtypetext" encrypted="" timeout="" advancedfind="" delay="" cleanup="1" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210029" scenariosection="" step="30">
		<text>Heading 2</text>
		<window />
		<key />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardkey" action="Press" timeout="10000" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210030" scenariosection="" step="31">
		<key key1="Enter" />
		<window />
	
	</command>
	<command type="keyboardtypetext" encrypted="" isremote="0" timeout="" advancedfind="" delay="" cleanup="1" commentedout="0" id="15979238545210031" scenariosection="" step="32">
		<text>So feel been kept be at gate. Be september it extensive oh concluded of certainty. In read most gate at body held it ever no. Talking justice welcome message inquiry in started of am me. Led own hearted highest visited lasting sir through compass his. Guest tiled he quick by so these trees am. It announcing alteration at surrounded comparison. 

Parish so enable innate in formed missed. Hand two was eat busy fail. Stand smart grave would in so. Be acceptance at precaution astonished excellence thoroughly is entreaties. Who decisively attachment has dispatched. Fruit defer in party me built under first. Forbade him but savings sending ham general. So play do in near park that pain. 

Old unsatiable our now but considered travelling impression. In excuse hardly summer in basket misery. By rent an part need. At wrong of of water those linen. Needed oppose seemed how all. Very mrs shed shew gave you. Oh shutters do removing reserved wandered an. But described questions for recommend advantage belonging estimable had. Pianoforte reasonable as so am inhabiting. Chatty design remark and his abroad figure but its. 

Imagine was you removal raising gravity. Unsatiable understood or expression dissimilar so sufficient. Its party every heard and event gay. Advice he indeed things adieus in number so uneasy. To many four fact in he fail. My hung it quit next do of. It fifteen charmed by private savings it mr. Favourable cultivated alteration entreaties yet met sympathize. Furniture forfeited sir objection put cordially continued sportsmen. 

Considered an invitation do introduced sufficient understood instrument it. Of decisively friendship in as collecting at. No affixed be husband ye females brother garrets proceed. Least child who seven happy yet balls young. Discovery sweetness principle discourse shameless bed one excellent. Sentiments of surrounded friendship dispatched connection is he. Me or produce besides hastily up as pleased. Bore less when had and john shed hope. 

And sir dare view but over man. So at within mr to simple assure. Mr disposing continued it offending arranging in we. Extremity as if breakfast agreement. Off now mistress provided out horrible opinions. Prevailed mr tolerably discourse assurance estimable applauded to so. Him everything melancholy uncommonly but solicitude inhabiting projection off. Connection stimulated estimating excellence an to impression. 

Friendship contrasted solicitude insipidity in introduced literature it. He seemed denote except as oppose do spring my. Between any may mention evening age shortly can ability regular. He shortly sixteen of colonel colonel evening cordial to. Although jointure an my of mistress servants am weddings. Age why the therefore education unfeeling for arranging. Above again money own scale maids ham least led. Returned settling produced strongly ecstatic use yourself way. Repulsive extremity enjoyment she perceived nor. 

Led ask possible mistress relation elegance eat likewise debating. By message or am nothing amongst chiefly address. The its enable direct men depend highly. Ham windows sixteen who inquiry fortune demands. Is be upon sang fond must shew. Really boy law county she unable her sister. Feet you off its like like six. Among sex are leave law built now. In built table in an rapid blush. Merits behind on afraid or warmly. 

In it except to so temper mutual tastes mother. Interested cultivated its continuing now yet are. Out interested acceptance our partiality affronting unpleasant why add. Esteem garden men yet shy course. Consulted up my tolerably sometimes perpetual oh. Expression acceptance imprudence particular had eat unsatiable. 

Impossible considered invitation him men instrument saw celebrated unpleasant. Put rest and must set kind next many near nay. He exquisite continued explained middleton am. Voice hours young woody has she think equal. Estate moment he at on wonder at season little. Six garden result summer set family esteem nay estate. End admiration mrs unreserved discovered comparison especially invitation. 

</text>
		<window />
		<key />
	
	</command>
	<command type="if" expression="%CloseWord_OnEnd% == 1" showelse="0" commentedout="0" id="15979238548530006" scenariosection="" step="33">
	
		<then commentedout="0" id="15979238548530007" scenariosection="" step="34">
		
			<command type="playscenario" stylename="playsnippet" scenariotype="Snippet" filename="Close_App_Name.xml" continueonfail="" statusvariable="App_Closed" commentedout="0" id="15979238548530011" scenariosection="" stepalias="If MS WORD is open close it" step="35">
				<variable1 variable="WindowTitle" vartype="String" expression="Word"></variable1>
				<variable2 variable="AppName" vartype="String" expression="WINWORD"></variable2>
				<variable3 vartype="String"></variable3>
				<variable4 variable="" vartype="Image" xsize="24" ysize="12"></variable4>
				<variable5 variable="DontSaveButton" vartype="Image" xpos="477" ypos="388" xsize="60" ysize="16">MS Word_Img1(1).bmp</variable5>
				<variable6 vartype="Image"></variable6>
				<variable7 vartype="String"></variable7>
				<variable8 vartype="String"></variable8>
				<variable9 vartype="String"></variable9>
				<variable10 vartype="Image"></variable10>
			
			</command>
		</then>
		<else commentedout="0" id="15979238548530008" scenariosection="" step="36">
		
		</else>
	</command>

<Usage><commandcontainer type="scenario" name="MS Wprd.xml"><command type="findbitmap"><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img1.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img1_alt1.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img1_alt2.bmp</bitmapname></command><command type="findbitmap"><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img2.bmp</bitmapname></command><command type="findbitmap"><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img3.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img3_alt1.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img3_alt2.bmp</bitmapname></command><command type="findbitmap"><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img4.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img4_alt1.bmp</bitmapname></command><command type="findbitmap"><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img5.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img5_alt1.bmp</bitmapname></command><command type="findbitmap"><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img6.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img6_alt1.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img6_alt2.bmp</bitmapname></command><command type="findbitmap"><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img7.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img7_alt1.bmp</bitmapname><bitmapname>MS Wprd_Img7_alt2.bmp</bitmapname></command></commandcontainer></Usage></commandcontainer>